<resources>
    <string name="about_content">"&lt;h1&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Daily Programmer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Welcome!!&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Welcome to r/DailyProgrammer! &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dailyprogrammer is about challenging programmers of all skill level with weekly programming challenges. 3 challenges a week are posted at increasing difficulty. Solutions are peer reviewed and redditors can ask for the community for feedback and comments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The typical posting of challenges occur on or near the following days.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Mon &lt;strong&gt;[Easy]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Wed &lt;strong&gt;[Intermediate]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Fri &lt;strong&gt;[Hard]&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Challenges are developed from ideas posted on /r/DailyProgrammer_ideas and ideas from the moderator team. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is important to keep in mind a few basic considerations of the difficulty. The difficulty of a challenge is rated roughly for the required knowledge, theory and effort required to complete. There does not exist a simple or easy measure of rating challenges. What might seem [Hard] might turn out to be [Easy] for some redditors while some [Easy] might be [Hard] for other redditors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Also note that the moderator team might not be able to post a challenge for an assigned day. This could be for many reasons. Although the moderator team strives to keep challenges posted as needed but if a challenge cannot or does not get posted, please consider looking or working on older challenges and continue to wait for the next challenge. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Why and Who&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Dailyprogrammer is for anyone who wants to improve or practice programming. There is no restriction to who can use this subreddit.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Why would you want to use this subreddit?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Learn a new language&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Practice software design&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Practice programming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Practice problem solving&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Keep your programming skills current&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Gain insights from peers &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Help others by offering code review&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Motivation to practice by solving problems&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;To have fun&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Novelty accounts are not entertained and will be banned. This is a discussion oriented sub. Although light hearted comments and discussions are welcome, any negative influence on the subreddit that trolls the users or hurts the community's harmony will be moderated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Solution Submission Tutorial&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;This tutorial aims to solve some of the common issues people have with submitting their solutions. Carefully follow the steps below; screenshots are provided to give you some context.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ensure your account is validated. You can check that your account is validating by opening your Reddit profile (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/DhpXYgd.png&quot;&gt;top-right of the page, click your username&lt;/a&gt;) and making sure the &lt;strong&gt;Verified Email&lt;/strong&gt; trophy appears in your profile description (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/1k4LIH0.png&quot;&gt;it looks like this&lt;/a&gt;). If your account is not verified, go to &lt;a href=&quot;/verify&quot;&gt;this page&lt;/a&gt; and follow the steps there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make sure you are not submitting your solution as a post (&lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/DAL2fv7.png&quot;&gt;via this button&lt;/a&gt;). This is the wrong button. You need to post solutions as comment replies to the challenge thread; carry on with the steps below.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Open the comment section of the challenge thread you wish to submit to. You can do this by clicking &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/SYnuRDk.png&quot;&gt;the comment button&lt;/a&gt; under the post name, and scrolling down past the challenge specification. Here you can view other people's submissions, and also post your own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Post your solution using the &lt;strong&gt;Submission Guidelines&lt;/strong&gt; below. To post a comment, find &lt;a href=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/FSDOU5q.png&quot;&gt;this reply box&lt;/a&gt; on the page, type your reply using the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/wiki/commenting&quot;&gt;reddit Markdown comment format&lt;/a&gt;, and click the &lt;strong&gt;save&lt;/strong&gt; button. Congratulations, your solution has been submitted!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you still have problems submitting a solution, message the moderators using &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fdailyprogrammer&quot;&gt;this link here&lt;/a&gt;, and thoroughly describe the problem you are having.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Submission Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;As always please keep Reddiquette http://www.reddit.com/wiki/reddiquette in mind when posting solutions and comments on solutions.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; To keep solutions from spoiling other redditor's attempts we ask post your solutions with 4 spaces before each line of code so that it will hide the solution as &quot;spoiler&quot; or use a 3rd party service like Github Gist https://gist.github.com/ (we do not recommend sites such as pastebin or pastie as submissions may be pruned over time).&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; It is recommended to preface your solutions by saying what language you used. Like if you solved it using Python, C, Javascript, Lisp, etc.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; If you are seeking feedback then by stating you like feedback will improve your chances of getting some feedback.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Feel free to submit more than 1 solution in more than 1 language. You are not restricted to only 1 solution in 1 language. &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Code &amp;amp; Peer Review Guidelines&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Posting your own solution is good but also taking a moment to comment or peer review other submissions really can help others. Please keep in mind a few of these points.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Be modest&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Be professional&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Avoid judgements&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Do offer suggestions and give examples&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Size does not matter. 1 line or 1000 lines. It is all good.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; There are no right or wrong ways. Just ways. There are many ways to solve a problem.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt; Never leave open suggestions that does not answer the question to &quot;Why&quot;. Why does it not work. Or Why should it be changed. Do not always focus on the negative. Take a moment to also comment on the positive. What did they do well or interesting.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Idea/Challenge Submissions&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;There exists a separate but connected subreddit for redditors to post their challenges. See /r/DailyProgrammer_ideas and post your challenges ideas.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Achievement Flair&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#MedalsIcon&quot;/&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Gold medals are awarded by moderators for smart solutions, impressive design or demonstration of good skills. Challenges that come from redditors who post on /r/DailyProgrammer_ideas will be awarded a Gold Medal if they do not already have one.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Silver medals are awarded by moderators for neat tricks, cool optimizations, creative solutions or even fun code. You can also earn a silver medal by submitting a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/dailyprogrammer/wiki/community&quot;&gt;community project&lt;/a&gt; - see below.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Community Projects&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you have your own DailyProgrammer-related project that you work on (or have worked on), then check out our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reddit.com/r/dailyprogrammer/wiki/community&quot;&gt;community project list&lt;/a&gt;! If you submit your project to this list and you haven't already got a silver flair medal, you will earn one if your project makes it onto the list.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Other Subreddits&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Reddit is full of great subreddits for programming. The following lists some other subreddits to check out. If you have a subreddit you like to use and it is not listed here that relates to programming please message the moderators to add it to these lists.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Programming Subreddits&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/DailyProgrammer_ideas - a place to submit your ideas for challenges for /r/dailyprogrammer&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/askprogramming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/coding&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/dailyscripts&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/learnprogramming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/problemoftheday&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/programming - news and discussion about programming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/Programmingprompts&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Programming Language Subreddits&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/AutoHotKey (AutoHotKey)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/c_programming (C)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/cpp (C++)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/cpp_questions (C++)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/cprog (C)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/csharp (C#)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/dartlang (Dart)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/elm (Elm)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/fsharp (F#)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/Haskell (Haskell)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/java (Java)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/javahelp (Java)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/javaTIL (Java)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/learnjava (Java)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/javascript (JS)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/objectivec (Objective-C)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/perl, /r/perl6 (Perl)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/python (Python)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/learnpython (Python)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/beginnerprojects (Python-based projects &amp;amp; challenges)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/ruby (Ruby)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/rails (Ruby on Rails)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/rubyonrails (Ruby on Rails)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/rust (Rust)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Libraries, Frameworks, APIs&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/dotnet&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/processing -- Processing.js&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Software Engineering Subreddits&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/coolgithubprojects&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/gamedev&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/programming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/progether&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Computer Science&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/algorithms&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/AskComputerScience&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/compsci&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/cscareerquestions&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/CSEducation&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/CSELI5&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Operating Systems&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/ios&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/iosdev&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/iosprogramming&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/simpleios&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/linux&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/linux4noobs&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Security&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/netsec&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Other&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/dmenu&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/proceduralgeneration&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/ProComputerTips&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/ProgrammerHumor&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/socialistprogrammers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;/r/CoolGithubProjects&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Special Thanks&lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks to /u/n0rs for the incredible banner and logo! Thanks also to /u/Pink401k for suggested improvements to the subreddit CSS.&lt;/p&gt;"</string>
    <string name="app_name">Programming Challenges</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="author_label">Challenge by:\u0020</string>
    <string name="description_favorite_button">Favorite button</string>
    <string name="description_completed_button">Completed button</string>
    <string name="description_share_button">Share button</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_about">About</string>
    <string name="nav_completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="nav_saved">Saved</string>
    <string name="nav_challenges">Challenges</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="sort_description">Sort button</string>

    <!--Ad unit id-->
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>
    <string name="AdUnitId">ca-app-pub-3474287381828825~1688212398</string>
    <string name="appwidget_text">DP Challenges</string>
    <string name="add_widget">Add widget</string>
    <string name="icon_description">Icon</string>
    <string name="zero">0</string>
    <string name="menu_descending">DESC</string>
    <string name="menu_ascending">ASC</string>
    <string name="heading_all">ALL</string>
    <string name="heading_easy">EASY</string>
    <string name="heading_medium">MEDIUM</string>
    <string name="heading_hard">HARD</string>
    <string name="header_description">DESCRIPTION</string>
    <string name="header_solutions">SOLUTIONS</string>
    <string name="title_programming_challenges">Challenges</string>
    <string name="label_challenge_id">EXTRA_CHALLENGE_ID</string>
    <string name="label_db_id">EXTRA_DB_ID</string>
</resources>
